<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Campervan Diary</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Campervan Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Holyhead</title>
      <link>/2019/09/06/holyhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/09/06/holyhead/</guid>
      <description> 2019-09-06 2 nights Wild camp at Porth Dafarch Campsite at Anglesey Outdoors  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appleby-in-Westmorland</title>
      <link>/2019/08/03/appleby-in-westmorland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/08/03/appleby-in-westmorland/</guid>
      <description> 2019-08-03 1 night Wild camp in Appleby  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe&#39;s Bob Graham</title>
      <link>/2019/06/21/joe-s-bob-graham/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/06/21/joe-s-bob-graham/</guid>
      <description> 2019-06-22 2 nights Wild camp in St Johns in the Vale Campsite at Dalebottom Farm  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul&#39;s Joss Naylor</title>
      <link>/2019/06/15/paul-s-joss-naylor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/06/15/paul-s-joss-naylor/</guid>
      <description>1 night Wild camp at Santon Bridge  Paul Tynan decided to have an attempt at the Joss Naylor Challenger and James was down to support leg 4 which covers the Wastdale Valley. I hiked up with James to the start of leg 4 which is at the stretcher box at Styhead. Once we had cheered Paul through, James ran off to do leg 4 and I ran back down into the valley with one of the leg 3 supporters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eskdale</title>
      <link>/2019/04/12/eskdale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/12/eskdale/</guid>
      <description>2 nights Eskdale Camp-site  James signed up to do the Eskdale Elevation race and we decided to make a weekend of it. I booked to stay in the lovely, but rather pricy Eskdale Campsite, mostly because it&amp;rsquo;s short walk from the start of the fell race. The minimum booking was for two nights, so we headed up after work on Friday night. Once we were all parked up, we decided to have a quick dash up the Great How.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Widdop Reservoir</title>
      <link>/2019/03/23/widdop-reservoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/23/widdop-reservoir/</guid>
      <description>1 night Wild camp at Widdop Reservoir  James had signed up for the Heptonstall Fell Race, and we decided to head over the night before for our first campervan trip of 2019. We were suitably excited.
I&amp;rsquo;d identified a lay-by alongside Widdop reservoir on Google maps that looked like an ideal park up spot. From the lay-by, we would only have a ten minute drive to Heptenstall village for the start of the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heysham Power Plant</title>
      <link>/2018/12/31/heysham-power-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/31/heysham-power-plant/</guid>
      <description>1 night Layby near Ocean Edge holiday park  Keen to start the new year in an adventerous manner, I decided we would do a local wild camp on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve. James, however, was more keen on having an early night. I won, so at 10pm, we bundled into the van and drove to the coast. My first two parking spots both had &amp;ldquo;No Overnight parking&amp;rdquo; signs, so had to get creative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Trossachs, Scotland</title>
      <link>/2018/09/14/scotland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/14/scotland/</guid>
      <description>3 nights Wild camp at Grey Mare&amp;rsquo;s Tail CL at Drummund Trout Farm  Set off on Friday night after work. We got to Moffat in time to get chips. Parked up at Grey Mares Tail. Some campervans but a quiet night. Up early in the morning, to have a quick run up to the tarn, before porridge and the drive up to the Trossachs.
We stopped at Callander to get a (second) veggie breakfast from Deli Ecosse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian&#39;s Joss Naylor attempt</title>
      <link>/2018/07/21/ian-s-joss-naylor-attempt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/21/ian-s-joss-naylor-attempt/</guid>
      <description>1 night Wild camp at Pooley Bridge  Ian was attempting the Joss Naylor, and James was supporting on leg one. This meant a 5am start from Pooley Bridge. Keen to use the van again, I suggested we camp up the night before, and found a small layby just outside Pooley Bridge where we could spend the night.
On the drive up, we stopped at Haweswater and walked up Branstree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arnside</title>
      <link>/2018/07/18/arnside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/18/arnside/</guid>
      <description>1 night Wild camp at Arnside Prom  Wednesday evening, James was out at running club. I decided spontaneously to do an overnight at Arnside.
I arrived in time to do a short 5k run, pop to the Albion for a pint, and then settle down in the van with a hot chocolate. It was a fairly busy spot, 3 other campervans and lots of passing traffic in the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Torver</title>
      <link>/2018/05/30/torver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/30/torver/</guid>
      <description>1 night Wild camp at Torver  My brother Tom and his girlfriend Pluggy were staying in the Lake District and we&amp;rsquo;d planned to go mountain biking in Grizedale. The night before, James and I drove up late to Torver for our first night in the campervan.
We&amp;rsquo;d eaten beforehand so it was just a case of parking up and getting to sleep. When we arrived, there was another campervan at the parking spot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>